tennisearth.com 2018-02-02

# Privacy Policy - TennisEarth.com

TennisEarth.com takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

1\. Our Policy  
We are committed to safeguarding and protecting the private information of every person who visits our website. Our Privacy Policy has been set out to let you know exactly what type of information we collect when you make use of the services on our website and why we collect it. We will also let you know what we do with that information once it has been collected.

2\. The type of information collected  
Any information which can be used to identify an individual is considered by us to be Personal Information. This data will include, but is not limited to:

2.1 Personal information about yourself such as - first and last names, date of birth, physical and email addresses, contact telephone numbers, shipping addresses, billing addresses, credit and/or debit card information.

2.2 Information relating to your transaction history with us such any purchases you may make or our goods or services.

2.3 Information about your computer which is held by us on our servers which are based in the UK and occasionally elsewhere. This information will include details about your visits to and use of this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, time and date of access, length and visit and number of pages viewed.

3\. Cookies  
Cookies are small text files of information sent by a web server to a web browser that are stored on your computer or equipment when you visit certain online pages. The information is sent back to the server every time a browser requests a page from the server. We use cookies to track use of our website. We also may use cookies to monitor traffic to the site, improve our service and make it easier and/or more relevant for your use. 

We may use different types of cookies on the website.   
A **'session-based'** cookie: This type of cookie is only allocated to your computer for the duration of your visit to our website. A session-based cookie helps you move around the website faster and, if you're a registered customer, it may allow us to give you information that is more relevant to you. This cookie automatically expires when you close your browser. 

A **'persistent'** cookie: This type of cookie will remain on your computer for a period of time set for each cookie. 

Please note that our advertisers and payment services providers may also send you cookies.

4\. Why we use cookies?  
We use cookies so that we can gather information which allows us to understand your preferences and provide you with more relevant information. They also allow us to confirm that you are a registered user and save your login details when accessing certain services on the website. In addition, we may use cookies to collect statistics on the use of our web-based services and also, in conjunction with web beacons (images that originate from a third part website to track visitor activity) , to ensure that our mailing tools are all working satisfactorily. 

Session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser but persistent cookies will remain on your computer until they expire or until they are permanently deleted. If you want to refuse or opt out of using cookies, you can usually modify your browser settings to decline them. The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. However, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to experience all of the interactive features on our website.

5\. How we use personal information  
Personal information and data submitted to the website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy. We may, therefore, use your personal information and data in the following ways:

5.1 To administer the website

5.2 To improve your experience when browsing the website

5.3 To supply you with any goods and/or services purchased via the website.

5.4 To collect payments from you for any goods/services supplied

5.5 To send you things such as newsletters or marketing communications relating to our website which we feel may be of interest to you

5.6 To provide third parties with statistical information about our users. However, this information will not be used to identify any individual user.

6\. Internet-based advertising  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please refer their respective websites.

7\. Disclosure  
We will disclose personal information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, payment processors, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as it is necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy. However, we may disclose your Personal Information if required to do so by law, or if We believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: 

7.1 comply with any legal process served on us, any of our sites or the service or in circumstances where We are under a substantially similar legal obligation. 

7.2 protect and defend our rights or property.

7.3 act to protect the personal safety of users of the service or the public. If we suspect you of fraudulent payment, including use of stolen credit cards, or any other fraudulent activity (including any chargeback or other reversal of a payment) or prohibited transaction (including money laundering), we reserve the right to share this information (together with your identity) with banks, credit card companies, and appropriate agencies.

8\. International transfers of data and information  
Personal information collected by ourselves via the website may be stored and processed in any country in which we or our affiliates, suppliers, ESPs or agents maintain facilities. By using our Service, you expressly consent to any transfer of information outside of your country (including other countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Areas). 

9\. Security of your personal information and data   
We will ensure that we take all reasonable precautions to prevent the loss or misuse of your personal information and data. All personal information provided by you will be stored on our secure password and firewall protected servers. However, due to the inherent insecurity of data transmission over the internet, we are unable to guarantee the security of data in transmission over the internet. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, we use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. 

10\. Children Under Age 13   
We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to us. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [underage@tennisearth.com](mailto:underage@tennisearth.com)

11\. Consent to the Privacy Policy and policy amendments   
By clicking 'Submit' or 'I agree' during the registration process or by your continued use of the Service following the posting of this Privacy Policy (as applicable), you agree to this Privacy Policy. This policy supersedes any earlier version previously posted on our website. This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with our Terms and Conditions and any additional applicable terms posted on our website. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy and will notify you of these changes by posting the modified terms on our website. We recommend that you revisit this Privacy Policy regularly.
